better-coupons.com 2015-06-09

# Better Coupons | Coupon codes, promo codes & discounts that work! | Better-Coupons.com

This privacy policy (“Policy”) discloses the data collection and use practices of Better-coupons (“Better-coupons”) in connection with the Better-coupons Web site (the “Web Site”) and all associated Better-coupons products and services (the “Better-coupons Services”). Better-coupons will not directly inform you of any changes to the privacy policy which involve use of your personal information. If at any time you are dissatisfied with our service to you or are in disagreement with our terms and conditions or privacy policy, you reserve the option to Opt-out of our website and future communication. Better-coupons may make non-significant changes to our privacy policy and may not notify our members if said changes do not pertain to the handling of personal information.

What Information We Collect/How We Use It

We store and use the information you give us in accordance with the terms of this Policy. Our registration form (or registration information you provide our marketing partners if you joined Better-coupons though one of our partners) requests that you provide certain contact and profile information. That information includes but may not be limited to: name, address, email address, phone number, gender and birth date. Additional information may include, but not be limited to, car and lifestyle information about you and your family such as marital status and household information (spouse, children, pets, etc.), ethnicity, education, income, occupation, purchasing habits, reading habits, insurance, and participation in research surveys. In addition, we might receive information about you from outside sources and add it to your Better-coupons membership information. We do this to improve personalization of our services (for example, providing better newsletter content, advertising or special offers that we think will interest you). We also may collect information such as the identification of the server your computer is logged onto and whether you opened a Better-coupons e-mail delivered to you. We also may compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending identical messages to our members. You can add and modify the information you have provided by sending an e-mail to information@Better-Coupons.com with your requested changes.

We use all this information in five ways:  
• to provide you with personalized information via electronic delivery, telemarketing and/or direct mail. These may include personalized offers from 3rd party sources.  
• to send you targeted advertising via electronic delivery and/or direct mail;  
• to contact you for feedback and surveys via electronic delivery and/or direct mail;  
• to send you general and administrative information about your Better-coupons membership via electronic delivery and/or direct mail; and  
• to provide your contact information to Better-coupons marketing partners whose offer(s) you have selected to receive in order for them to send you special offers via electronic delivery, telemarketing and direct mail.

How Is Such Information Used?

Better-Coupons will use your non-personal information in order to better target advertisements and to improve our advertising systems and products.

Third Party Information Gathering

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Better-Coupons.com will not share any Non-PII data with any third parties.

Cookies

We use cookies on the site to deliver personalized content. Many Web browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. You may change your browser settings to either reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is about to be placed on your computer. Please note, however, that rejecting cookies while visiting the Better-coupons Web Site may result in certain parts of the Better-coupons Web Site not operating correctly or as efficiently as if they were allowed.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.

E-mail Links

In some instances we may include certain links in our e-mails that will allow us to monitor whether you access specific content or advertisements contained in that e-mail. When you click on one of these links, we will record that click and certain activities on the Web page associated with that link. We may use this information for various purposes, such as to conduct internal research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior in and to our e-mail advertisements and content, and to better understand and serve you.

Disclosures

Better-coupons may disclose information about you and your use of the Better-coupons Web Site and the Better-coupons Services if Better-coupons believes such disclosure is reasonably necessary: (i) to comply with the law or legal process; (ii) to protect or defend the rights or property of Better-coupons or others; (iii) to enforce the Better-coupons Terms and Conditions or this Privacy Policy; and (iv) to respond to claims that the content(s) of a communication violates the rights of another. In addition Better-coupons may share or transfer information about you and that you provide to Better-coupons, to one or more third party entities pursuant to a sale, merger, assignment, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of a portion, or all of, the assets or stock of Better-coupons or its affiliated entities, or as otherwise provided herein.  
Reports

We periodically prepare analyses and reports reflecting visitor and member use of the Better-coupons Web Site and Better-coupons Service for our internal use as well as for a limited number of our business partners. These reports include aggregate (non-personal) information about Better-coupons members, and in certain instances, visitors to the Better-coupons Web Site. The information in these reports will not identify you individually. Our business partners who have access to these reports will not be able to contact you from the information contained in the reports.

Links

The Better-coupons Web Site, as well as the electronic messages sent as part of the Better-coupons Service, may contain links to other sites or services. Better-coupons is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party sites. If you have a question about the privacy policy of those other sites, please contact them directly.  
Removal

To have all of your personally identifiable information removed from our database, send an e-mail request to information@Better-Coupons.com and we will be happy to delete such information after we receive a request to that effect. Please be advised that by requesting that your data be removed from our database, you will be unsubscribed from the Better-coupons Service.  
Updates

Better-coupons may revise this Policy from time to time and at any time in the future to (i) improve or modify the Better-coupons Service, (ii) reflect future developments in Better-coupons data information gathering, storing and release practices, (iii) comply with applicable laws, and (iv) reflect changes in Better-coupons business structure. Depending on the nature of the change, we will notify users by e-mail (to the current e-mail address on file) and/or placing a notice on the Better-coupons Web Site.  
Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

Better-Coupons.com  
2232 South Nellis Blvd.,  
Suite G 3 #311 Las Vegas, Nevada 89104  
Email: information@Better-Coupons.com
